Register to the Papers of Vladimir and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
Yale University Music Library
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1885-1991; Series III; 20 boxes (8.3')
  - Toscanini Photographs, III.D
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1901; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 166)
      Verdi's body being moved to the Casa Verdi
    - Arturo Toscanini and Gatti-Casazza, 1904; 3 items. (Box 57, Folder 166)
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1905; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 167)
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1907-8; 2 items. (Box 57, Folder 167)
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1908; 3 items. (Box 57, Folder 167)
      Photographs of 2 drawings
    - Arturo Toscanini and Carla Toscanini, 1908-1910?; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 167)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Carla Toscanini, Polo, and others, 1909; 3 items. (Box 57, Folder 167)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Walter Toscanini, and others, 1910; 5 items. (Box 57, Folder 168)
      Monte Rosso, Metropolitan Opera, etc.
    - Arturo Toscanini and Sandra Frigerio, 1914; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 169)
    - Arturo Toscanini, ca. 1914-1918; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 169)
      WWI front
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1915; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 169)
      Arena in Milan
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1916; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 169)
    - Arturo Toscanini conducting army orchestra, 1917 Aug. 31; 2 items. (Box 57, Folder 169)
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1918; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 169)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and Gabriele d'Annunzio, 1920; 3 items. (Box 57, Folder 170)
      La Scala tour, etc.
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1921-1929; 2 items. (Box 57, Folder 170)
      2 copies of postcard with caricature by Autori
    - Arturo Toscanini and orchestra, 1924; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 170)
      Zurich
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, and others, 1924-1926; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 170)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, and others, 1926; 17 items. (Box 57, Folder 171)
      Brussels, North Cape, New York, Salzburg - includes duplicates
    - Arturo Toscanini, Pizzetti, Zoltßn Kodßly, Carla Toscanini, and others, 1927-1928; 9 items. (Box 57, Folder 172)
      New York, Villa d'Este
    - Arturo Toscanini, Adriana Clementi, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Aldo Finzi, Carla Toscanini, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Walter Toscanini, Miecio Horzowski, Roberto Foligno, and others, 1929; 23 items. (Box 57, Folder 173)
      Aboard the S.S. Augustus and the train to Berlin with La Scala - Berlin, Naples, and New York
    - Arturo Toscanini, Polo, and Mrs. Max Smith, 1920s; 1 item. (Box 57, Folder 173)
      Viareggio
    - Arturo Toscanini, Yehudi Menuhin, Siegfried Wagner's grandchildren, Eva Chamberlain, Carla Toscanini, Winifred Wagner, Max Smith, Siegfried Wagner, King Ferdinand of Bulgaria, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Walter Toscanini, Countess Gravina, and others, 1930; 64 items. (Box 57, Folder 174-176)
      New York, Bayreuth, Isola Pescatori, Parma, and Naples - some duplicates
    - Arturo Toscanini, Irene Serkin, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Gregor Piatigorsky, W. Wagner, Bruno Zirato, Furtwängler, Tietjen, Princess Wrede, and Carla Toscanini, 1931; 41 items. (Box 57, Folder 177-178)
      Aboard the S.S. Bremen, Casa Holmes, Bayreuth, Isolino S. Giovanni, aboard the S.S. Berengano?, St. Moritz, Port Washington, Cherbourg
    - Arturo Toscanini, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Maria Da Zara, Carla Toscanini, E. Polo, Foligna, Walfredo Toscanini, Gatti-Casazza, Countess Cimi, Aldo Tamai, B. Zirato, Mimy Finzi, Riccardo Luzzatto, A. Finzi, V. Tommasini, Mimi Zuccari, ? Marra, Fred Muschenheim?, and Margherita De Vecchi, 1932; 33 items. (Box 57, Folder 179)
      New York, Cherbourg, Isolino dei Cesari, Long Island, and Carnegie Hall
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, and others, 1932; 24 items. (Box 58, Folder 180)
      Isolino S. Giovanni - 12 negatives laid in
    - Arturo Toscanini, Raffaele Calzini, Emil Ludwig, M. De Vecchi, Nina Morgana, Maria Rota, Holebrand, Pizzetti, Mrs. Coolidge, Krausse, Larisch, and Mara, 1933; 26 items. (Box 58, Folder 181)
      Milan, New York, Isolino S. Giovanni, Port Washington, and Hampton Bay
    - Arturo Toscanini, members of the Philharmonic, 1934; 2 items. (Box 58, Folder 182)
    - Symphony Orchestra (N.Y.), and others, 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 18)
      Large photo of dinner at the Hotel Astor, New York, and Bayreuth
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Huberman, Steinberg, Lotte Lehman, N.Y. Philharmonic, and Eleonora von Mendelssohn?, 1936; 13 items. (Box 58, Folder 183)
      Tel Aviv, Salzburg, and Egypt
    - Arturo Toscanini, Bruno Walter, Stefan Zweig, E. Polo, and Arnaldo Fraccaroli, 1937; 5 items. (Box 58, Folder 184)
    - Arturo Toscanini and Carla Toscanini, [1937?]; 6 items. (Box 58, Folder 184)
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1938; 18 items. (Box 58, Folder 185)
      New York and the Hague? - some duplicates
    - Carla Toscanini, Walter Toscanini, and family?, 1938; 9 items. (Box 59, Folder 186)
      New York - 4 negatives laid in
    - Arturo Toscanini, Pauline Chotzinoff, Sonia Horowitz, Carla Toscanini, Vladimir Horowitz, E. Polo, Mrs. Saitzoff, Milstein, Heifetz, Wallenstein, R. Serkin, and Adolf Busch, 1939; 22 items. (Box 59, Folder 187)
      New York, Riverdale (N.Y.), Chatham School of Music, Luzern, and the Grand Canyon - includes photos for Life and Vogue
    - Arturo Toscanini, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Carla Toscanini, and Pizzetti, 1930s; 10 items. (Box 59, Folder 188)
      Isolino S. Giovanni and St. Moritz
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and [Ferruccio?] Calusio, 1940; 1 item. (Box 59, Folder 189)
      Teatro Colon
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and Charles O'Connell, 1940-1941; 5 items. (Box 59, Folder 189)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Mr. and Mrs. Giuseppe De Luca, Frances Alda, Martinelli, and Maria Jeritza, 1942-1945; 11 items. (Box 59, Folder 190)
      Riverdale
    - Arturo Toscanini, Walter Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, 1944-1946; 5 items. (Box 59, Folder 191)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Cantelli, and Verdali, 1948-1949; 10 items. (Box 59, Folder 192)
      Riverdale and Milan
    - Arturo Toscanini, 1940s; 5 items. (Box 59, Folder 193)
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Walter Toscanini, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, David Sarnoff, Al Walker, and Cia Toscanini, 1950; 25 items. (Box 59, Folder 194)
      Isolino S. Giovanni and aboard train for NBC tour
    - Arturo Toscanini, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Mme. Finzi, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Rose Bampton, Moscona, Terese Braibanti, Wallenstein, Duke Acquarone, Emanuela Acquarone, and Walter Toscanini, 1954-1958; 27 items. (Box 59, Folder 195)
      Milan, Isolino S. Giovanni, Philadelphia, and Riverdale
    - Arturo Toscanini, 5 items. (Box 59, Folder 195)
      Photographs taken of television by James Watson (Autograph letter signed enclosed, 1987 Mar. 23) - "it was next to last appearance of A.T. in this country"
    - Concert by Serkins at Riverdale marking the opening of the Toscanini Archives, etc., 1964-1967; 4 items. (Box 59, Folder 196)
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Emanuele Castelbarco and Pierfilippo Acquarone, [Renato Fasano?], [Aldo Moro?], and others, ca. 1967 Mar. 25; 31 items. (Box 59, Folder 196)
      E. Piccagliani, photographer, Teatro alla Scala and Foto "Meljtta" de Ferrari & Paterlini, photographers, Parma - Milan and Parma - 100th anniversary of Arturo Toscanini's birth
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Emanuele Castelbarco and Pierfilippo Acquarone, and others, ca. 1967 Mar. 25; 6 items. (Box 59, Folder 196)
      [Casa di Riposo per Musicisti, Milan?]
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, George Schick, and Nicolo Moscona, 1974; 1 item. (Box 59, Folder 196)
      Manhattan School of Music
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Isaac Stern, 1989 Mar.; 2 items. (Box 59, Folder 196)
    - Arturo Toscanini and Arturo Toscanini's study in Milan, 4 items. (Box 59, Folder 197)
    - Arturo Toscanini, n.d. (Box 59)
      Arturo Toscanini at Riverdale - decoupage on wood
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and Sonia Horowitz, 9 items. (Box 59, Folder 197)
  - Photo Albums, III.E
    - Album belonging to Regina Horowitz? Scriabin?, Blumenfeldt, Vladimir Horowitz, Simenon, Sophie, Regina, and George Horowitz, Regina's daughter, Lena, granddaughter, Olia, and husband, ? Lieberman, George's son, Petia, and his son, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Neuhaus, Prokofiev, and Siloti, pre 1925-1965; 24 items. (Box 60, Folder 198)
      postcard laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Carla Toscanini, and Emanuela Castelbarco, 1934-1936; 157 items. (Box 60, Folder 199-203)
      Milan, Lido/Venice, Cortina, Isolino S. Giovanni, Valmont, Paris, Salzburg, and Badgastein
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Emanuela Castelbarco, and others, 1937-1939; 77 items. (Box 60, Folder 204-207)
      Isolino S. Giovanni, Gstaad, and Venice
    - Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Walter Toscanini, Walfredo Toscanini, Nathan Milstein, Rudolf Serkin, and others, 1941-1942; 91 items. (Box 60, Folder 208-211)
      Riverdale, "Wave Hill," and California
    - Sonia Horowitz, Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and others, 1942 Apr.; 27 items. (Box 61, Folder 212)
      Riverdale - Sonia Horowitz's first communion
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Maria Callas, Marc Chantellier, Katya Kovalski, Emanuela Castelbarco Acquarone, and others, 1970-1972; 66 items. (Box 61, Folder 213-215)
      Paris, Milan - album belonging to Sonia Horowitz
    - Negatives of photographs taken of the photograph albums by the New York Times, 97 items. (Box 61, Folder 216)
      Typed letter signed (copy) from the New York Times to Wanda Toscanini Horowitz laid in
- CLIPPINGS, 1876-1991; Series IV; 8 boxes (3.3')
  The clippings are arranged chronologically with the exception of several subject groups which appear in the chronological list filed under the date of the earliest article. The clippings have been copied onto acid-free paper, and the originals discarded. Clippings which were already photocopied were not recopied onto acid-free paper.
  - Clippings about Vladimir Horowitz, IV.A
    - 1876 Dec. 21, 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 1922-1923, 6 items. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - 1926, 8 items. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 1926-1986, 38 items. (Box 62, Folder 4)
      Clippings and program from Hamburg concerts from 1926-1929 assembled by fan, Irma Lyss
    - 1927, 10 items. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 1928, 16 items. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - 1929, 11 items. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 1930, 5 items. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - 1931, 4 items. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - 1932, 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - 1933, 3 items. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - 1934, 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - 1935, 6 items. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - 1937, 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - 1939, 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - 1940, 6 items. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - 1941, 4 items. (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - 1942, 9 items. (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - 1943, 10 items. (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - 1944, 3 items. (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - 1945, 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - 1946, 7 items. (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - 1948, 4 items. (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - 1949, 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - 1950, 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - 1951, 5 items. (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - 1952, 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - 1953, 14 items. (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - 1954, 2 items. (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - 1955, 15 items. (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - 1956, 58 items. (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Undated clippings from a folder labeled "1956 and earlier", 35 items. (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - 1957, 174 items. (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - 1958, 27 items. (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Undated clippings from a folder labeled "1958-1961", 12 items. (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - 1959, 26 items. (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - 1960, 20 items. (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - 1961, 12 items. (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - 1962, 2 items. (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - Billboard clippings, 1962; 7 items. (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - Billboard clippings, 1963; 49 items. (Box 63, Folder 41-42)
    - 1964, 3 items. (Box 63, Folder 43)
    - 1965, 60 items. (Box 63, Folder 44)
    - Billboard clippings, 1965; 55 items. (Box 63, Folder 45-46)
    - 1966, 11 items. (Box 63, Folder 47)
    - Billboard, 1966; 51 items. (Box 63, Folder 48)
    - 1967, 12 items. (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - 100th anniversary of Arturo Toscanini's birth, 1967; 14 items. (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - Billboard, 1967; 36 items. (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - 1968, 90 items. (Box 64, Folder 51-52)
    - Billboard clippings, 1968; 26 items. (Box 64, Folder 53)
    - From album labeled "Horowitz on TV", 1969; 30 items. (Box 64, Folder 54)
    - 1970, 3 items. (Box 64, Folder 55)
    - 1972, 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 56)
    - 1973, 6 items. (Box 64, Folder 57)
    - 1974, 71 items. (Box 64, Folder 58-59)
    - 1975, 78 items. (Box 65, Folder 60-61)
    - 1976, 102 items. (Box 65, Folder 62-63)
    - 1977, 44 items. (Box 65, Folder 64-65)
    - 1978, 176 items. (Box 65, Folder 66-69)
    - 1979, 86 items. (Box 66, Folder 70-71)
    - 1980, 33 items. (Box 66, Folder 72)
    - 1981, 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 73)
    - 1982, 6 items. (Box 66, Folder 74)
    - 1983, 8 items. (Box 66, Folder 75)
    - 1984, 2 items. (Box 66, Folder 76)
    - 1985, 3 items. (Box 66, Folder 77)
    - 1986 Jan.-Apr., 166 items. (Box 66, Folder 78-81)
    - Collection of French press revues of Horowitz in Moscow compiled by Agence France Presse, 1986 Apr.; 68 items. (Box 66, Folder 82)
    - 1986 May, 159 items. (Box 66, Folder 83-85)
    - Collection of German press revues of Horowitz recitals in Berlin and Hamburg, 1986 May; 135 items. (Box 67, Folder 86)
      Compiled by the Berliner Festspiele, in 1987
    - 1986 June-August, 53 items. (Box 67, Folder 87)
    - 1986 September-October, 25 items. (Box 67, Folder 88)
    - 1986 November-December, 68 items. (Box 67, Folder 89-90)
    - 1987 January-February, 29 items. (Box 67, Folder 91)
    - 1987 March-May, 65 items. (Box 67, Folder 92)
    - 1987 June-October, 42 items. (Box 67, Folder 93)
    - 1987 November-December, 206 items. (Box 67, Folder 94)
    - 1988, 37 items. (Box 67, Folder 95)
    - 1989 January-October, 43 items. (Box 67, Folder 96)
    - 1989 November 6, 83 items. (Box 68, Folder 97-98)
    - 1989 November 7-10, 31 items. (Box 68, Folder 99)
    - 1989 November 11-28, 42 items. (Box 68, Folder 100)
    - 1989 December 1-15, 85 items. (Box 68, Folder 101)
    - 1989 December 16-24, 79 items. (Box 68, Folder 102)
    - 1989 December 25-29, 56 items. (Box 68, Folder 103)
    - 1989 December 26-31, 62 items. (Box 68, Folder 104)
    - 1990 January 1-3, 31 items. (Box 68, Folder 105)
    - 1990 January 4, 186 items. (Box 69, Folder 106-107)
    - 1990 January 5, 57 items. (Box 69, Folder 108)
    - 1990 January 6-12, 79 items. (Box 69, Folder 109)
    - 1990 January 13-31, 37 items. (Box 69, Folder 110)
    - 1990 February-December, 96 items. (Box 69, Folder 111-112)
    - 1991, 26 items. (Box 69, Folder 113)
    - n.d., 102 items. (Box 69, Folder 114-116)
  - Clippings about Arturo Toscanini, IV.B
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1967; 6 items. (Box 70, Folder 117)
    - Arturo Toscanini's retirement, 1954 Apr. 5-8; 6 items. (Box 70, Folder 118)
    - Arturo Toscanini's death, 1957 Jan.-Mar.; 80 items. (Box 70, Folder 119-122)
- SCRAPBOOKS, 1928-1989; Series V; 9 boxes (3.75')
  There are a total of 29 scrapbooks containing clippings, photographs, correspondence (including many telegrams), programs, advertisements, and miscellaneous items. Twenty-six have been microfilmed and an acid-free copyflo has been made from the microfilms. There are 5 reels of microfilm. Numbers have been assigned (by Yale University Music Library for filming) to each scrapbook, which are arranged in chronological order. The box, reel, and frame numbers, and the inclusive dates are listed for the copyflo of each scrapbook.
  An additional 3 scrapbooks have been photocopied onto acid-free paper and microfilmed. The microfilm is laid in.
  The original scrapbooks have been disassembled and the original correspondence, photographs, programs, advertisements, and miscellaneous items filed in their corresponding series. Cross-references have been made to the scrapbooks, and there are pencil notes on the items or their acid-free wrappers. The original clippings were discarded for preservation purposes. The clippings in part duplicate those in IV. CLIPPINGS.
  There is another microfilm containing several copies of 9 clippings. This microfilm came with the Papers and no copyflo has been made since it is not a scrapbook and the articles are all in IV. CLIPPINGS.
  - Microfilm of 26 scrapbooks containing clippings, photographs, correspondence, programs, advertisements, and miscellaneous items, 1928-1989 (Box 70)
  - Scrapbook #1, copyflo printouts, 1931-1940 (Box 134)
  - Scrapbook #2, copyflo printouts, 1941-1947 (Box 134)
  - Scrapbook #3, copyflo printouts, 1948-1950 (Box 135)
  - Scrapbook #4, copyflo printouts, 1951 Sep.-Dec. (Box 135)
  - Scrapbook #5, copyflo printouts, 1949-1954 (Box 136)
  - Scrapbook #6, copyflo printouts, 1962-1963 (Box 136)
  - Scrapbook #7, copyflo printouts, 1963 Jan.-Dec. (Box 137)
  - Scrapbook #8, copyflo printouts, 1964 Jan.-Dec. (Box 137)
  - Scrapbook #9, copyflo printouts, 1965-1966 (Box 137)
  - Scrapbook #10, copyflo printouts, 1965-1967 (Box 137)
  - Scrapbook #11, copyflo printouts, 1965-1966 (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #12, copyflo printouts, 1966-1967 (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #13, copyflo printouts, 1968-1969 (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #14, copyflo printouts, 1968 Aug.-Oct. (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #15, copyflo printouts, 1968 Jan.-Dec. (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #16, copyflo printouts, 1968 Jan.-Dec. (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #17, copyflo printouts, 1970-1974 (Box 138)
  - Scrapbook #18, copyflo printouts, 1975-1976 (Box 139)
  - Scrapbook #19, copyflo printouts, 1978 Apr.-Aug. (Box 139)
  - Scrapbook #20, copyflo printouts, 1976-1985 (Box 139)
  - Scrapbook #21, copyflo printouts, 1978-1979 (Box 139)
  - Scrapbook #22, copyflo printouts, 1979-1985 (Box 139)
  - Scrapbook #23, copyflo printouts, 1983-1985 (Box 140)
  - Scrapbook #24, copyflo printouts, 1985-1986 (Box 140)
  - Scrapbook #25, copyflo printouts, 1986-1989 (Box 140)
  - Scrapbook #26, copyflo printouts, 1985-1987 (Box 140)
  - Microfilm of 9 clippings, 1943-1953 (Box 70)
    (several copies of each clipping on reel). Copies of clippings filed with IV. CLIPPINGS
  - Microfilm of 3 scrapbooks containing clippings, programs, ticket stubs, and jottings, 1932-1939 (Box 70)
  - Photocopies of scrapbooks: "Europe", 1932-1939 (Box 141)
  - Photocopies of scrapbooks: "Europe", 1935-1936 (Box 141)
  - Photocopies of scrapbooks: "Europe", 1938 (Box 141)
- CONTRACTS, ROYALTY AND BOX OFFICE STATEMENTS, AND EXPENSES, 1928-1989; Series VI; 15 boxes (6.25')
  This series is divided into three subseries: A. Concerts; B. Recordings; and C. Bills, Receipts, and Expenses. The first subseries is further divided into: 1. Contracts, box office statements, etc. (arranged chronologically by concert date with all items pertaining to a concert together); 2. Management contracts, legal actions, and pay stubs (arranged by subject, then chronologically); and 3. Route books, schedules, and concert information (arranged either chronologically or by concert hall within each subject group). Subseries B and C are arranged chronologically within each subject group.
  Some correspondence from important persons who are listed in I.A. CORRESPONDENCE - Personal, has been copied and the originals filed with I.A, the copies remaining with the contracts. Notes appear on the items or their folders when this has been done and cross- references have been made in the register. Fan mail included with the contracts has not been copied and remains with the contracts. A cross-reference appears in the register from I.B. CORRESPONDENCE - Subject.
  - Concerts, VI.A
    - Contracts, box office statements, etc., VI.A.1
      Contracts, box office statements, scalings, seating plans, duplicate programs, press releases, visa applications, itineraries, pay stubs, and housing arrangements. Includes cancellations and postponements (postponed concerts are filed under the later date)
      - Tallahassee, Philadelphia, Wheeling, WV, Columbia, MO, Albany, Chicago, St. Louis, Carnegie Hall, Montreal, Providence, Carnegie Hall, NBC broadcast, Detroit, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Denver, Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, New Orleans, Denton, Tex., Shreveport, LA, Chicago, 1933-1934; 26 items. (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Pasadena, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Newark, NJ, Philadelphia, Carnegie Hall, Chicago, Toronto, Cleveland, Boston, Carnegie Hall, St. Louis, Chicago, Minneapolis, Ottawa, Indianapolis, Atlanta, Brooklyn, Pittsburgh, Carnegie Hall, Washington, D.C., Carnegie Hall, Ravinia, Ill., Hollywood, CA, Robin Hood Dell, PA, 1939-1940; 29 items. (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Ann Arbor, Toledo, Oberlin, Detroit, Chicago, Denver, Portland, OR, Seattle, Spokane, Dallas, Houston, Carnegie Hall, Kansas City, MO, Chicago, Birmingham, AL, Durham, NC, Washington, D.C., Carnegie Hall, White Plains, Philadelphia, Scranton, Columbus, OH, New Haven, Boston, Ames, IA, Kalamazoo, MI, Carnegie Hall, Hamilton, Canada, Carnegie Hall, Los Angeles, Claremont College, Sacramento, Salt Lake City, 1941; 34 items. (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Rochester, Chicago, Carnegie Hall, Chicago, Newark, NJ, Philadelphia, St. Louis, Boston, Worcester, MA, Hartford, Toledo, Indianapolis, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Oberlin, Minneapolis, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Santa Barbara, Fort Worth, Columbia, MO, Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Milwaukee, Wellesley, MA, Portland, ME, Providence, Cincinnati, Minneapolis, Portland, OR, Seattle, 1942; 35 items. (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Brooklyn, Cleveland, Chicago, Richmond, VA, Buffalo, Pittsburgh, Newark, NJ, Washington, D.C., Birmingham, Atlanta, New Orleans, Chicago, Carnegie Hall, Milwaukee, Carnegie Hall, Chicago, Milwaukee, Carnegie Hall, Louisville, Washington, D.C., Cincinnati, Louisville, 1943; 26 items. (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Birmingham, Savannah, Rochester, Carnegie Hall, Chicago, Dayton, Pittsburgh, Trenton, Hunter College, Brooklyn, Boston, Baltimore, Washington, D.C., Rutgers, Philadelphia, Columbus, Cincinnati, Ann Arbor, Detroit, Minneapolis, Carnegie Hall, Chicago, Birmingham, Memphis, New Orleans, Atlanta, Knoxville, St. Louis, Baltimore, Newark, NJ, Chicago, Carnegie Hall, Philadelphia, Savannah, Jacksonville, Carnegie Hall, Washington, D.C., 1944-1945; 46 items. (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - San Diego, Fresno, Los Angeles, Pasadena, Portland, OR, Seattle, San Francisco, Sacramento, Boston, Chicago, Minneapolis, Omaha, Cleveland, Chicago, Rochester, Buffalo, Carnegie Hall, Cincinnati, Bloomington, IN, Pittsburgh, Louisville, Baltimore, Washington, D.C., Philadelphia, Carnegie Hall, Hartford, Springfield, MA, Boston, Carnegie Hall, Chicago, Montreal, 1945-1946; 51 items. (Box 71, Folder 7)